Like seven seconds
七秒钟
So one page should be the best fit
所以一页应该是最合适的
And please use no more than two pages
请不要超过两页
Try to make it clean
尽量把它弄干净
Simple
简单
Professional and short
专业和短期
The second thing is that don't put your photos on your resume
第二件事是不要把你的照片放在简历上
They're looking for software engineers
他们在找软件工程师
Random models
随机模型
So even yourself is really gorgeous
所以连你自己都很美
Please don't put your photos as no one cares
请不要把你的照片，因为没人在乎
And also with through space
也通过空间
The third thing to remember is that don't use colorful things
第三件要记住的是不要用五颜六色的东西
Like a section filled with red or green
就像一个充满红色或绿色的部分
And another section in white
另一部分是白色的
The fourth thing is that the structure
第四件事是结构
The header section would always be our contact information
标题部分将永远是我们的联系信息
And then there are three main sections from top to bottom If you're a student or a new graduate You can push your education after contact information rather than skills
然后从上到下有三个主要部分 如果你是一名学生或新毕业生 你可以在联系方式而不是技能后推动你的教育
Because you are pretty much just a new graduate and student
因为你只是个刚毕业的学生
And don't have too many experiences yet
还没有太多的经验
The last thing is that the file name of your resume can be your name
最后一件事是简历的文件名可以是你的名字
Dash role
破折号角色
You're applying for years of experience for students
你申请的是有多年工作经验的学生
Just your name dash dash university
只有你的名字破折号大学
Let's talk about the contact information
我们来谈谈联系方式
You want to make your full name and prefer name above all
你想做你的全名，最喜欢名字
And then your email address
然后你的电子邮件地址
Phone number location in a smaller font size
较小字体大小的电话号码位置
Maybe attach a github link or your linkedin
也许可以附上一个GitHub链接或你的LinkedIn
If you feel really comfortable about it
如果你真的觉得很舒服
The first main section is skills
第一个主要部分是技能
The first point is that you need to include your programming languages technologies like docker Message two And your languages like english or mandarin Remember we don't say chinese We say mandarin
第一点是，您需要包括诸如Docker之类的编程语言技术 信息二 你们的语言像英语或普通话 记住我们不说中文 我们说普通话
The second point is that you don't necessarily have to raise your skills
第二点是你不一定要提高你的技能
Like using stars or different levels
比如用星星或者不同的等级
And the third point is that you need to read the job descriptions
第三点是你需要阅读工作描述
And see what kind of skills they are looking for and tailor your resume scale section
看看他们在寻找什么样的技能，并为你的简历量身定做部分
Accordingly
因此
It will help you to pass the automatic screening system in the match skills as many as possible
它将帮助你尽可能多地通过自动筛选系统中的比赛技能
The next thing is you only pull the skills when you are sure that you can interview with
接下来的事情是，只有当你确定你可以面试
Someone
有人
May have just watched several videos about python and have never written any code
可能只是看了几个关于Python的视频，从来没有写过任何代码
And he or she certainly are not able to have an interview about python
他或她肯定不能接受关于Python的采访
So don't put it
所以不要把它
The fifth thing is do we need to include excel skills
第五件事是我们需要包括Excel技能吗
Please don't do that
请不要那样做
Don't write some obvious things like windows Mac os Visual studio code Word powerpoint You are wasting your space The second main section is working experience The first point is to make all experiences relevant
不要写一些明显的东西，比如Windows Mac OS Visual Studio代码 Word PowerPoint 你在浪费你的空间 第二个主要部分是工作经验 第一点是让所有的经验都相关
So if you want to apply for a software engineering role
所以如果你想申请一个软件工程角色
Please don't put your internships in library or in the kfc
请不要把你的实习机会放在图书馆或肯德基
This is very important
这很重要
And don't put those small jobs
别把那些小工作
And cramming them into your one page resume
把它们塞进你一页纸的简历里
The second point is that we want to order our experiences from the latest one
第二点是我们想从最新的经验中排序
From top to bottom
从上到下
They are more focused on the recent jobs and experiences
他们更关注最近的工作和经历
Rather than internships ten years ago
而不是十年前的实习
The third thing is how to write each experience
第三件事是如何写每一次经历
You will write the role or position
你将写角色或职位
And the company name
以及公司名称
And the time with both months and yeah
两个月的时间是的
Then you will use from three to five bullet points
然后你会用三到五个要点
To show the most important things in each project You will use the past to describe Like designed Rather than design You will not use subjects like i he she they we
展示每个项目中最重要的东西 你将用过去来描述 就像设计的 而不是设计 你不能用我他她他们我们这样的话题
If you have been a tutor for computer science class in your university
如果你在你的大学里当过计算机科学课的导师
You are new graduates
你们是刚毕业的
Who does not have too many experiences
谁没有太多的经验
You can also put this
你也可以把这个
It's one experience with
这是一次与
Only like one or two bullet points to briefly introduce what you have done
只有一两个要点来简单介绍一下你做了什么
Data of your success
你成功的数据
So the last question is the core part of the experience
所以最后一个问题是体验的核心部分
How to write a good bullet point to describe your work
如何写一个好的要点来描述你的工作
I have summarized a formula for you guys to quickly on board
我总结了一个公式给你们快速上船
To this english resume
到这份英文简历
E plus i ng plus g
E加i ng加g
Or by the edmeans
或者通过edmeans
To use past form to describe what you have done in the past
用过去的形式来描述你过去所做的事情
The i n
我在
G means what is the result of your work And please give a number or data to show your success The last i ng or buy to introduce what kinds of techniques or tools you have used
G的意思是你工作的结果是什么 并请给出一个数字或数据来显示你的成功 最后一次介绍你使用了什么样的技术或工具
Like rest api redis then comes another cool part
就像休息API Redis一样，然后是另一个很酷的部分
Please assess your impact by quantifying it
请通过量化来评估你的影响
You said you have done a really good job
你说你做得很好
But how good it is
但它有多好
They don't know
他们不知道
So use like increased twenty percent revenue
所以使用像增加了20%的收入
Increase the ability to ninety eight percent to show your work
将展示作品的能力提高到98%
And dong used too many technical details as recruiters and north of engineers
董用了太多的技术细节作为招聘人员和工程师
Please give an overall general description of your accomplishments
请大致描述一下你的成就
But not dive into too many details
但不要钻研太多细节
Like use word protocol and how to optimize each parameter in your deep learning models
比如使用Word协议以及如何优化深度学习模型中的每个参数
Just give a brief overview
只需简要概述一下
Like optimizing the models and increases its accuracy to ninety five percent
比如优化模型并将其精确度提高到95%
Or some people just use a docker to establish a stable framework To deploy microservices And they tend to put too many details on their resume list every step Including how to build and poor images and give every parameters
或者有些人只是用一个码头工人来建立一个稳定的框架 部署微服务 他们倾向于在简历清单上每一步都写上太多的细节 包括如何建立和糟糕的图像，并给出每个参数
But please don't do that
但请不要那样做
As you can just say
就像你刚才说的
The stability of the system reaches reaches ninety nine percent
系统的稳定性达到百分之九十九
Outperforming the traditional system
超越传统系统
Several simple sentences would bring your success to your life
几个简单的句子会给你的生活带来成功
The last section is about your education
最后一节是关于你的教育
Please make sure that you have your university name degree in the graduation
请确保你在毕业典礼上有你的大学名称学位
Year and month on it
上面有年份和月份
If you have a good gpa or ranking
如果你有很好的GPA或排名
Please put it as well
请把它也放进去
If you also have really impressive awards
如果你也有令人印象深刻的奖项
You can have another role to list them
您可以有另一个角色来列出它们
Don't put irrelevant awards like instruments
不要把无关的奖项像乐器一样
Remember for new graduates or students
应届毕业生或学生请记住
Make me section on the top of the resume
让我在简历的顶部部分
But for experienced software engineers
但对于有经验的软件工程师来说
Please don't put too much effort into this section and make it too long Recruiters will care more about your skills and working experience Okay
请不要在这一节上花太多的精力，把它弄得太长 招聘人员会更关心你的技能和工作经验 好啦
I have listed all critical tips
我列出了所有的关键提示
Both
两者都是
You should reduce the decrease the hydrogen Decrease
你应该减少氢气的减少 减少
When in the stable to
在马厩里的时候
Just stand alone
孤军奋战
O bin here that could
这里的垃圾箱可以
That could be in here
可能在这里
Now go in my beautiful father goggle
戴上我父亲的护目镜
Like on your shoulder
就像在你的肩膀上
And going to sit on
准备坐在
And your alert
你的警觉
Your alert
你的警报
Your on
你上
Your monitoring system
你的监控系统
Push the accident and why i should go
推事故和我为什么要去
And it's all there from which you guys
就在那里，你们
From the
从
Go to a go to must love you Don't change it all A single sit on and your go to
去去一定要爱你 不要改变一切 一坐下你就去
Cropping tied the cross platform
裁剪绑跨平台
Jin had a platform platform to form
金有一个平台平台形成
Like the egg apple as young in time about the fish on that
就像鸡蛋苹果一样年轻的时候关于鱼在那
Total for the giant for capability
巨人的能力总额
Don't know when the end to end
不知道什么时候结束
So don't don't don't go
所以不要不要走
Donuts
甜甜圈
You don't put the mind
你不把思想
You don't
你不知道
So don't
所以不要
So don't do this in rule Mized now Let's take a look at what vocabulary in software engineering
所以不要在规则中这样做 现在变小了 让我们来看看软件工程中的哪些词汇
Can help you to describe your project in your resume
可以帮助你在简历中描述你的项目
If you want a template to build your
如果您想要一个模板来构建您的
If you want
如果你想
If you want a template to build your resume
如果你想要一个模板来构建你的简历
I have one and please follow me and messaging me
我有一个，请关注我，给我发短信